

+92.333.6307210



mkamran.malik72@gmail.com



Gulberg 3, Lahore, Pakistan

Summary

A results-driven, customer-focused, articulate and analytical Senior Web Developer who can think "out of the box." Strong in design and integration problem-solving skills. Expert in Laravel, Wordpress, Bootstrap, Html5, Css3, Javascipt, Jquery, Vue.js, and MySql with database analysis and design.

Experienced in:

Engineering web development, all layers, from database to services to user interfaces

Analysis and design of databases and user interfaces

Managing requirements

Implementing software development lifecycle policies and procedures

Managing and supporting multiple projects

Highly adaptable in quickly changing technical environments with very strong organizational and analytical skills.

Work Experience in short:

E-commerce

Payment Gateways(Stripe, Paypal, Authorize.Net)

CRM Hubspot Integrations

Pusher Integration

Twilio Integration

Store Locator Integration (Bullseye)

Google Maps

Ads Management system and preview

SEO Management

Social media (Posts, Comments, Likes, Share, Friendship)

Real Time Chat System

Real Time Notifications

Social Sharing, Social Login

Blogger, Forum, Article Writing or Sharing

Rest API's

Binary Point system

Job portal

Admin Dashboard and Management

Wordpress all type customization and creation

Experience

Dec 2017 - Present **Senior Laravel Developer** Odbytes, Lahore, Pakistan Nov 2016 - Dec 2017 Web Developer TechEsthete, Lahore, Pakistan Im Working in TechEsthete as a Web Developer My duty from 10:00 am to 07:00pm Feb 2015 - Feb 2016 **Tutor** Self, Vehari, Pakistan I was a Tution Teacher during my Masters 5 to 7 students was studied at a time as my part time work Jun 2014 - Nov 2014 Salesman Zong Franchise, Haroonabad, Pakistan I was a Salesman at Zong franchise for 6 month during my study for part time

Education

2016 COMSATS Institute of Information Technology
Masters in Science , masters in computer science
Computer Science

Skills

Angular Js	Less than 1 Year	ASP.net	Less than 1 Year
Bootstrap	2 Years	C#.Net	Less than 1 Year
C++	1 Year	Codelgniter	Less than 1 Year
CSS	2 Years	Data Structure	Less than 1 Year

DATABASE	2 Years	Git	2 Years
Html	2 Years	JavaScript	2 Years
Jquery	2 Years	Laravel	2 Years
Laravel Homestead	1 Year	Microsoft Office 2003	2 Years
Microsoft office 2007	2 Years	Multi Tasking	2 Years
MySQL	2 Years	РНР	3 Years
version control	1 Year	Vue.js	1 Year
Wordpress	2 Years		

Projects

Ghani Cloth House

http://ghaniclothhouse.com/

Study Relations

https://studyrelations.com/

OdXtra

https://odxtra.com/

Recastly

http://app.recastly.net/dashboard

Pelchat

https://pelchat.wpengine.com

Supportyourhospital

http://supportyourhospital.ca

Afterdarkdistillery

https://www.afterdarkdistillery.com

dpffilter are sells their spare parts or filter of cranes buses and

large v

https://www.envolveenergy.com

Dpffilter

https://www.dpffilters.ca/

Dbase Recreation

http://139.162.249.243/tog-sales/dbase/dashboard.php

Leopard Money

http://leopardmoney.com/

Rome By Segway

https://www.romebysegway.com/

School Management and Online System

http://bigdream.ca/

interestfreehousing

http://interestfreehousing.ca

eTharapyPro

https://etherapypro.com/

photo-api

http://

metroryde

http://www.metroryde.com/

http://www.cpcstrategy.com/

http://writing test cases and working on another small module

gameworn

http://34.199.158.185

Online Automatic Question Paper Generator

http://

Languages

Saraiki

Intermediate

Punjabi

Expert

Urdu

Expert

English

Intermediate

